# Jessica Wise

#### **SUMMARY**

Experienced Customer Success Advocate with 4+ years of experience improving customer experiences, looking to further develop my career in UX Design and UX Development. Previously responsible for nurturing client relationships, ensuring client happiness, retention and concerns with the templated Real Estate web solutions. Assisted clients with editing the templated solution with custom CSS and JS to better fit personal branding and web site needs. Experience with working closely with sales, renewals, marketing and product teams to ensure client feedback is used to make data driven decisions and improvements to the product. Outgoing self-starter with a passion to learn and grow in any setting.

Looking to help companies grow and evolve their products to meet internal and external client needs and expectations. Keenly interested in innovation-driven startups looking to make a footprint in the tech community.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Placester, Inc.**, **Boston**, **MA** — Support UX Engineer

JAN 2018 - MAR 2018

- Managed onboardings and client happiness for a Book of Business that consisted of Real Estate Agents and Brokers of varying technical background
- Exceeded client expectations by providing HTML and CSS skills along with JS knowledge to better customize the templated solution to match clients' personal branding and website needs that the templated website could not provide
- Assisted with internal testing of CSS and JS changes to the templated websites
- Assisted clients and coworkers with editing of logos and pictures to better fit within the templated websites
- Understood client needs and expectations and achieved a 5 star CSAT survey rating for all months employed

## **Rogue Wave Software, Boston, MA** — *Customer Success Advocate*

JAN 2017 - JAN 2018

- Worked with the sales team and clients directly to understand what the client's short and long-term goals were, and how we could utilize our onboardings, webinars and tech calls to support them in achieving those goals
- Tasked to spearhead the research to reduce customer churn rate
- Conducted extensive client research in regard to license operations
- Supported the company in a full redesign of the license operations strategy
- Provided Sales, Renewals and Marketing teams with my technical expertise on our entire suite of products and the capabilities that could be beneficial to the client's needs at hand
- Managed 1000+ client accounts with 6 to 100 end users including Verizon, TD Bank, CGI, Google and USDA

## **Performance Foodservice, Springfield, MA** — *Contract Coordinator*

APR 2015 - DEC 2016

- Worked directly with all Area Managers and District Managers in the handling of pricing of customer accounts and account maintenance
- Assisted the Multi-Unit Representative with pricing and needs of corporate or franchised customers at large scale
- Attended and helped with regional sales events
- Internally assisted training new hires in the contract coordination position

173 Main St Apt 1 Malden, MA 02148 (413) 727-5977 jessica.lee.wise@gmail.com jessicawise.github.io/jessicawise/

#### **EDUCATION**

Columbus College of Art and Design (CCAD) Bachelor of Fine Arts in Animation 2012

General Assembly UX Design 2018

#### **HIGHLIGHTS**

**Customer Oriented** 

Creative Thinker

Problem Solver

Able to work with all teams of varying sizes

Tech-savvy

### **KNOWLEDGE BASE**

SQL

HTML

CSS

Photoshop

Illustrator

Sketch

Invision

SCRUM/Agile

Web Design

Microsoft Office

Salesforce.com

Desk.com

Jira